<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Open Source Contributions on Jason Reeves</title>
    <link>https://jasonareeves.com/projects/contributions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Open Source Contributions on Jason Reeves</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jasonareeves.com/projects/contributions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GO-Fastly updates</title>
      <link>https://jasonareeves.com/projects/contributions/go-fastly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasonareeves.com/projects/contributions/go-fastly/</guid>
      <description>Go Fastly is a Golang API client for interacting with most facets of the Fastly API.
There was an API endpoint missing from the go-fastly API client, Event Logs. I added the event logs endpoint to the package as well as all the tests. I also noticed that the returned objects for the dictionary objects and items were not up to date so I updated those as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portauthority</title>
      <link>https://jasonareeves.com/projects/contributions/portauthority/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasonareeves.com/projects/contributions/portauthority/</guid>
      <description>Port Authority is a solution that I helped develop at Target. I was included in the development after it was 1&amp;frasl;2 way complete. I was able to enable scanning of images pulled from Docker Hub (exisiting functunality was to scan images from private repos), as well as create a drone.io plugin to enable pipeline scanning of a container in github enterprise. It was my first real world experience with Go and API development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atom-Hugo Fixes</title>
      <link>https://jasonareeves.com/projects/contributions/atom-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasonareeves.com/projects/contributions/atom-hugo/</guid>
      <description>The Atom plugin that allows users to launch a Hugo server with live refresh.
 On every hugo server lanuch, three or four pages would open instead of the one. The hugo server would not shutdown on macOS when wanting to exit.  I took this oportunity to fix the issue, as well as learn CoffeeScript to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>